It has begun. Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series
Yay!
This is Moa Chainsawa from Ukka. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, I'm Karen Watashibana, the generation and his wife. Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
Glad to meet you.
Thank you very much.
This time, it's a dialogue.
I've met you quite often, but it's not often that I get to talk to you like this.
It's not often that I get to talk with you like this, is it?
Well, I'm quite shy in the dressing room and so on.
Tomoku-san only talks to Miyu-chan.
That's right.
Miyu is the only one I can talk to, so I'm glad to hear that.
I'm shy too.
I usually don't talk to anyone.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes, I am. I'm glad to see you today.
I hope we can be friends today.
I'm looking forward to it.
When I was looking for something in common with you and Moa-chan...
You got in through a scout.
I'm the same way, so we have that in common.
That's right. You were scouted as an idol at Momokura-san's concert.
I wanted to be an idol, too, so I joined as a scout.
So we have that idol thing in common.
Thank you very much.
You aspire to be an idol?
That's right. I'm happy to do it.
Thank you very much.
Your new song is really good, too.
But you've had three songs out recently.
What was it?
Tail Mind
Aftanoo
Afternoon Laffety.
Very good!
That's the one.
It's not my best work, but...
It's Uguka's current song.
I haven't told them about the current song, but I've been pushing it a lot.
I've been watching their live videos and looking back on them.
Like the current picture.
I see. Do you look at other aspects when you do that?
My live videos?
Hmm? Mine?
No, it's not. Tomoku-san's.
Oh, Tomoku-san's?
Tomoku-san's dream is Tomoku-san's.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
Thank you very much
You always say that.
Thank you very much.
So, about this time...
I was wondering if we could ask each other some questions.
I've been thinking about it.
Well, thank you very much. By all means.
You are the leader, aren't you, Tomoku-san?
I'm not a leader at all.
I'm not a leader at all, but there are discussions among the members.
In such a situation, there are many opinions, such as A, B, and so on.
How do you decide?
How do you organize the members?
Yes, I do. I'm a leader, but I'm not a leader at all.
I'm not a leader at all.
I see.
That's right. Yuna is more solid than me.
She often organizes things.
But Tomoku-san is more likely to talk and make a majority decision.
But we don't clash so much.
I see.
We all go gaga together.
I get the impression that you have a strong sense of unity.
It's like an athletic club.
Athletic.
I see. Like majority rule.
I'm more likely to be told this by the manager than by the other members.
I'm often told by the manager, "This is the way to do it.
I see.
When it comes time to make a decision, it's pretty much like...
I'm like, "What should I do?
That's why I'm really interested in it.
I see. I heard that you decided on the tour.
I heard that you guys decided on the set for the tour together.
That's exactly what we did.
The first song is very important, isn't it?
That was also a problem.
Even after that, it wasn't always decided in a flash.
It is difficult to decide on the set.
It's difficult. Everyone has a different feeling about it.
So it was difficult.
Yes, it was. It turned out to be a good feeling.
It's a good feeling.
I took into account the manager's opinion.
I finally settled on it.
It's difficult.
Is it like that?
It's like that.That's how I feel.
You've got a good head on your shoulders.
I have a question for you, too.
When I saw you perform live...
I was really attracted to your singing and dancing.
It really caught my attention.
How do you practice singing?
I was wondering how you practice your singing.
But I'm pretty good.
I'm also a dancer.
I prefer to be told what to do.
If you have a clear idea of what you're supposed to do
I don't know how to say it.
It's easier for me to do.
I tend to do what my voice teacher tells me to do
I tend to do what I'm told by my voice teacher.
If it's me
For example, when I'm recording
I have a low voice.
When I'm recording
I make my voice sound like a bow.
I do that.
But that's not the voice they're looking for.
That's not the voice they're looking for in most cases.
So if I'm asked to sing in a brighter tone
If I'm asked to sing in a brighter tone
I focus on the brighter side that day.
It depends on each member.
Each member does his own thing.
That's very serious.
That's nice.
Thank you very much.
It's nice.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
I see.
You're a great dancer and stuff.
Not hip-hop, but like a dancer.
When I saw your dance practice...
What was that?
She walks in front of you.
He's got these amazing shoulders.
It's so cool.
I like that.
I know, right?
Cosmic wort?
That's it.
But it's...
I don't know.
That song is pretty hard to play.
But...
Tohoku-san's dancing is quite lively.
You know...
What was it?
Burning Heart
I really like it.
I've seen the video of it, right?
I've forgotten how many times I've seen it.
I've seen it so many times.
But I think we both like
Burning.
I love it so much.
Trophy girl.
I love it.
Thank you so much.
They step on each other's dance steps.
Comical.
Yes, it is.
Do you have a routine before a live performance?
I don't have a routine.
But that's exactly what we do.
The format of voicemail has changed recently.
The format of voicemail has changed.
I see.
It's a little different.
Like 8,000 steps.
I record them myself.
And then we play it together.
Oh...
It's like...
If I play it, they'll do it with me.
It's the same trend.
I see.
It's pretty much a routine now.
Like patting them on the back.
Yes.
Solo is the best.
The best?
I've had the members try it a few times.
It's just...
I don't know, it's not strong enough.
It's just not the right position.
Thank you.
But Solo's in a good place.
Solo's looking good.
Who is Mr. Tork?
Mr. Tork, but he usually
He usually does it with Kaja.
He's like, "Kaja, give me a squeeze, and then give me a bang.
And then he's like...
Kaja's good, he's not so good.Kaja's good, he's not so good.
I told him to go a little harder.
I see.
Thank you very much.
He's got a lot of personality.
Yes, he does.
Like your routine before a live performance.
Uka is like that.
You're solid.
No, she's not.
You're the eldest?
I'm the eldest.
But with Uka, she's always had lower skin.
I don't know, in places.
I'm not sure if she's strong in some areas.
But basically, I rely on her.
That's right.
She's cute.
But of all the TALK members...
You're the leader, but you're younger than the others.
That's right.
But he's really solid.
Not solid at all.
How were you chosen as the leader?
It was kind of sudden.
It was like, "We'll make an announcement at the concert.
Miyui, the new member, brought a letter.
Karen will be the leader.
It was an announcement like that.
Oh! I was like "Oh!
I was surprised, wasn't I?
Surprised.
And I'm not the type of person who can say anything out loud.
I've always wondered why.
But you know what?
It's because I can't say things out loud.
On the contrary...
Isn't there something like that?
The leader...
I've been told that.
That's great.
I see.
But Ayame is like a leader.
That's right.
Ayame has been the leader since a couple of years ago.
I see.
Even before that, she was a part of Uguka.
She was also a member of the girls' garden.
She's been in charge of the group for quite a while.
and MC for us.
He's so cool!
Thank you very much.
I'd like to say thank you.
It's the same with the lineage.
I guess it's just the number of people.
They're different.
That's why I wonder what it's like before a live performance.
I wonder what it's like before a live performance.
I'm really curious.
Before a gig?
I'm usually pretty busy.
I usually push.
I see.
It never starts on time.
Maybe when I went to the show...
I might have pushed it a little.
I'm sorry.
I usually do.
I'm kind of flailing around.
I'm just trying to get the engine together.
I have a really quick question.
How do you put hair together, member?
A while ago...
I don't know if it was before the staff was amazing or before...
Before, the staff would decide for me.
But recently, we've been able to do hair ornaments
But recently, we've been able to use costumes to make hair ornaments.
So we'd play rock-paper-scissors with the hair ornaments.
Whoever wins gets to wear whatever they want.
Rock-paper-scissors?
Every time or during the live performance?
What's it like?
We play this and that.
Let's do this, let's do that.
It's a group line. It's almost a "first come, first served" kind of thing.
I see.
Like, "Pony Perot's not working today.
Like that.
But there's a lot of people here, Mr. Tagita.
And we're not all on the same page.
You said you used to have them decide for you.
I was wondering how it's going now.
Rock-paper-scissors.
We'll just play rock-paper-scissors for now.
I see.
Parallel.
That's fair.
I was nervous,
And I'm shy,
I was nervous because I'm shy, but there were some differences within the group,There are quite a few things that are different within the group,
I was thinking that maybe we could incorporate the haircut rock-paper-scissors,
I thought it would be good for everyone.
Thank you very much.
She is also common as a group,
I had not had a chance to talk to her individually,
I was very happy to meet her,
I hope to get to know her a lot better,
Please look forward to the second part.
Thank you very much.